- id: ckw-l29-5075
  prompt: ""
  answers:
    - アクション
  hint: "noun"
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: ckw-l29-5077
  prompt: ""
  answers:
    - ヘッド
  hint: "noun"
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: ckw-l29-5086
  prompt: ""
  answers:
    - サークル
  hint: "noun"
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: ckw-l29-5125
  prompt: ""
  answers:
    - リンク
  hint: "verbal noun (する verb)"
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: ckw-l29-5148
  prompt: ""
  answers:
    - スポット
  hint: "noun"
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: ckw-l29-5150
  prompt: ""
  answers:
    - アレルギー
  hint: "noun"
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: ckw-l29-5155
  prompt: ""
  answers:
    - セキュリティー
  hint: "noun"
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: ckw-l29-5161
  prompt: ""
  answers:
    - スケジュール
  hint: "noun"
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: ckw-l29-5162
  prompt: ""
  answers:
    - スムーズ
  hint: "な-adjective"
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: ckw-l29-5165
  prompt: ""
  answers:
    - ゲスト
  hint: "noun"
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: ckw-l29-5169
  prompt: ""
  answers:
    - ハム
  hint: "noun"
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: ckw-l29-5173
  prompt: ""
  answers:
    - ミリグラム
  hint: "noun/counter"
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: ckw-l29-5174
  prompt: ""
  answers:
    - コレクション
  hint: "noun"
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: ckw-l29-5192
  prompt: ""
  answers:
    - ベビー
  hint: "noun"
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: ckw-l29-5196
  prompt: ""
  answers:
    - エピソード
  hint: "noun"
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []
